{
    "subject": "resource/Carl_Braden",
    "predicate": "property/politicalAffiliation",
    "object": "resource/Progressive_Party_(United_States,_1948)",
    "human_readable": "Carl Braden was affiliated with the Progressive Party (United States, 1948).",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9723301529884338,
            "question": "In what year was Carl Braden affiliated with the Progressive Party?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9237455129623413,
            "question": "What was the significance of Carl Braden's affiliation with the Progressive Party?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.911576509475708,
            "question": "Which country's Progressive Party was Carl Braden associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8600330948829651,
            "question": "What political party was Carl Braden affiliated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7490721940994263,
            "question": "Were there any other prominent figures associated with the Progressive Party in 1948?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6416300535202026,
            "question": "What is known about Carl Braden's political affiliations?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49188297986984253,
            "question": "Was Carl Braden involved in any political movements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3615169823169708,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the Progressive Party (United States)?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33747580647468567,
            "question": "What were the main goals or platforms of the Progressive Party in the United States during that period?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3286106586456299,
            "question": "Did Carl Braden hold any political offices?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Carl Braden was affiliated with the Progressive Party (United States, 1948).",
            "html": "dbpedia_6880_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were the main goals or platforms of the Progressive Party in the United States during that period?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6880_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about the Progressive Party (United States)?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6880_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was Carl Braden involved in any political movements?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6880_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6880_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6880_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6880_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6880_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6880_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6880_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6880_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6880_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6880_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6880_47.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information and the query \"Carl Braden was affiliated with the Progressive Party (United States, 1948).\", I will evaluate whether the information in the documents supports this triple.\n\nHere is my evaluation:\n\n* The documents mention that Carl Braden, along with his wife Anne, involved themselves in Henry Wallace's run on the Progressive Party for the presidency in 1948. This suggests that Carl Braden was indeed affiliated with the Progressive Party.\n* There are no contradictory statements or information in the documents that would suggest otherwise.\n\nTherefore, my evaluation is:\n\n`{'output': 'yes'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Carl Braden was affiliated with the Progressive Party (United States, 1948).\" Specifically, it mentions that \"The Bradens campaigned for the Progressive Party in 1948.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}